Inventory of the Charles Patrick Carroll papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Research materials
  - Schorn, Hubert, Der Richter im Dritten Reich, 1959 (Box 64)
  - Seraphim, Hans-Günther, 1950-1975 (Box 64)
  - Simpson, Nora Ann, 1962-1989 (Box 64)
  - Stammler, Rudolf, 1986 (Box 64)
  - Story, Joseph, 1970-1971 (Box 64)
  - Supreme Court decisions, 1971-1973 (Box 64)
  - Schmitt, Carl, 1914-1976 (Box 65)
  - Scholl, Hans and Sophie, 1980 (Box 65)
  - Sex problems in law, 1966 (Box 65)
  - Shockley, William, 1973 (Box 65)
  - Simon, Yves, 1945 (Box 65)
  - Siniavskii, Andrei, 1973 (Box 65)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr Isaevich, 1971-1983 (Box 65)
  - "State Power over Human Fertility and Individual Liberty", 1972 (Box 65)
  - Koessler, Maximilian, "Euthanasia in the Hadamar Sanitorium and International Law", 1953 (Box 65)
  - Walter, Franz, Die Euthanasie und die Heiligkeit des Lebens. Die Lebensvernichtung im Dienste der Medizin und Eugenik nach christlicher und monistischer Ethik, 1935 (Box 65)
  - Stangl, Franz, 1975 (Box 66)
  - Sterilization and abortion, 1927-1989 (Box 66)
    Includes a 1943 report on sterilizing Jewish women in mixed marriages
    - Buck vs. Bell, 1927 (Box 66)
    - Beal v. Doe, 1977 (Box 66)
    - Burns v. Alcala, 1975 (Box 66)
    - Cruzan v. Director, Missouri Department of Health, 1989 (Box 66)
    - Planned Parenthood of Central Missouri v. Danforth, 1976 (Box 66)
  - Štěpán, Jaromír, Právní odpovědnost ve zdravotnictvi, 1960 (Box 66)
  - Stern, Fritz, 1961 (Box 66)
  - Strafrecht (criminal law)
    - Deutsche strafrechtliche Landesreferate zum 8. Internationalen Kongress für Rechtsvergleichung, Pescara, 1971 (Box 66)
    - Die Geschichte der Abschaffung der Todesstrafe in der Bundesrepublik Deutschland, 1952 (Box 66)
    - Das kommende deutsche Strafrecht: Bericht über die Arbeit der amtlichen Strafrechtskommission, 1935-1936 (Box 66)
    - Liberales oder autoritäres Strafrecht?, 1933 (Box 66)
    - Nationalsozialistische Strafrechtspolitik, 1938 (Box 66)
    - Die neuere Entwicklung in der strafrechtlichen Beurteilung der Vernichtung der menschlichen Leibesfrucht aus medizinischen Gründen, 1933 (Box 66)
    - Reichsstrafgesetzbuch nach dem neuesten Stand der Gesetzgebung; Leipziger Kommentar, 1944 (Box 66)
    - Strafrecht des Arztes, 1968 (Box 66)
    - Die Tötung auf Verlangen und die Beteiligung am Selbstmord im schweizerischen, deutschen und französischen Strafrecht, 1964 (Box 66)
    - Yamashita vs. Styer, 1946 (Box 66)
  - Strauss, Leo, 1953 (Box 66)
  - Strughold, Hubertus, 1974 (Box 66)
  - Suicide, 1953 (Box 66)
  - Calvin, John, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Descartes, Rene (Box 67)
  - Ecumenism, 1978-1983 (Box 67)
  - Embryos, 1976 (Box 67)
  - Galton, Francis, 1869 (Box 67)
  - Gedenkstätte Plötzensee, 1968 (Box 67)
  - Gilson, Etienne, 1938 (Box 67)
  - Goebbels, Joseph, 1971 (Box 67)
  - Holocaust
    - US atrocities, 1980 (Box 67)
    - Understanding Nazi Germany, 1975-1983 (Box 67)
    - Church under the Nazis, 1974-1984 (Box 67)
    - Survivors, 1983-1991 (Box 67)
    - Spies, 1979 (Box 67)
    - War Criminals, 1972-1982 (Box 67)
  - Pisar, Samuel, Of Blood and Hope, 1980 (Box 67)
  - Reinisch, Franz, 1968 (Box 67)
  - Skinner, B.F., 1972-1979 (Box 67)
  - Smith, Adam, 1975 (Box 67)
  - Social Darwinism, 1979 (Box 67)
  - Socialism, 1970 (Box 67)
  - Society For The Protection Of The Unborn (SPUC) (Box 67)
  - Sociobiology, 1979 (Box 67)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr, 1978-1994 (Box 67)
  - Sorokin, Pitrim, 1941 (Box 67)
  - Sperm banks, 1982 (Box 67)
  - Sterilization, 1934-1995 (Box 67)
    Includes Die psychiatrischen Aufgaben bei der Ausführung des Gesetzes zur Verhütung erbkranken Nachwuchses: klinische Vorträge im erbbiologischen Kurs by Karl Bonhoeffer
  - Stern, Fritz, The Path to Dictatorship, 1918-1933, 1967 (Box 67)
  - Stress, 1975 (Box 67)
  - Student unrest, 1970-1974 (Box 67)
  - Suenens, Le´on Joseph, 1970 (Box 67)
  - Suffering, 1971-1987 (Box 67)
  - Sühnezeichen, 1977-1978 (Box 67)
  - Technology, 1992 (Box 68)
  - Terrorism, 1975-1988 (Box 68)
  - Thermodynamics, 1983 (Box 68)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 1942 (Box 68)
  - Thucydides, 1951 (Box 68)
  - Tiso, Jozef, 1947 (Box 68)
  - Torture, 1973-1976 (Box 68)
  - Translations, 1968-1971 (Box 68)
  - Transplantation
    - Blood, 1987 (Box 68)
    - Cadaver organs, 1964-1984 (Box 68)
    - Ethics, 1966-1988 (Box 68)
    - Heart, 1969-1987 (Box 68)
    - Kidneys, 1967-1972 (Box 68)
    - Law, 1968-1972 (Box 68)
    - Liver, 1989 (Box 68)
    - Medical, 1969-1988 (Box 68)
    - Psychological aspects, 1973 (Box 68)
    - Rhetoric, 1982-1987 (Box 68)
    - Tissue, 1966-1970 (Box 68)
  - Treblinka, 1979 (Box 68)
  - Triage, 1975-1986 (Box 68)
  - Tunte, Wilhelm, 1971 (Box 68)
  - Ultimate issues: a report, 1985-1993 (Box 68)
  - Ultrasound, 1988 (Box 68)
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1975-1989 (Box 68)
  - United for Life, 1970 (Box 68)
  - United Handicapped Federation, 1986 (Box 68)
  - United Nations, 1973 (Box 68)
  - United States Catholic Conference, 1986 (Box 68)
  - Violence, 1970-1983 (Box 69)
  - Virchow, Rudolf, 1953 (Box 69)
  - Vivisection, 1930-1979 (Box 69)
  - Voegelin, Eric, 1971-1985 (Box 69)
  - Volcom (Value of Life Committee), 1975-1991 (Box 69)
  - Volk, Ludwig, 1980 (Box 69)
  - von Clausewitz, Karl, 1973-1982 (Box 69)
  - von Fabrice, Heinrich, Die Lehre von der Kindsabtreibung und vom Kindesmord: gerichtsärztliche Studien, 1911 (Box 69)
  - von Galen, Clemens August, Graf, 1934-1981 (Box 69)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1930-1982 (Box 70)
  - Waldheim, Kurt, 1986 (Box 70)
  - War, 1969-1973 (Box 70)
  - Ward, Barbara, 1975 (Box 70)
  - Weber, Max, 1949-1991 (Box 70)
  - Weil, Simone, 1952 (Box 70)
  - Wiesel, Elie, 1986-1988 (Box 70)
  - Wiesenthal, Simon, 1979-1994 (Box 70)
  - Wildlife, 1975 (Box 70)
  - Wilhelmsen, Frederick D., 1978 (Box 70)
  - Williams, Robert H., 1969 (Box 70)
  - Willibald (Box 70)
  - Wallenberg, Raoul, 1979-1980 (Box 70)
  - Tagore, Rabindranath, 1980s (Box 71)
  - Theology, 1979-1988 (Box 71)
  - Theology and life, 1960-1973 (Box 71)
  - Theology of the laity, 1956-1987 (Box 71)
  - Tillich, Paul, 1974 (Box 71)
  - Tinder, Glenn, The Political Meaning of Christianity, 1989 (Box 71)
  - Turner, James, 1987 (Box 71)
  - Vernoff, Charles E., 1986-1987 (Box 71)
  - Vitz, Paul C., 1977 (Box 71)
  - "Weg, Stil und Konsequenzen urchristlicher Mission," by Peter Stuhlmacher, 1980 (Box 71)
  - Wilson, Woodrow, 1986 (Box 71)
  - Wolfson, Harry Austryn, 1987 (Box 71)
  - Women
    - Woman as slave to man under Nazis, 1974 (Box 71)
    - Ordination, liberation, feminism, etc., 1981-1989 (Box 71)
    - Millionairesses, working mothers, etc., 1973-1974 (Box 71)
    - Working women, 1981 (Box 71)
  - Work ethic, 1982 (Box 71)
  - Worship, 1970-1987 (Box 71)
  - Wurm, Theophil, 1953 (Box 71)
  - Wyzanski, Charles E., 1965 (Box 71)
  - Xenophon (Box 71)
  - Yad Vashem, 1986 (Box 71)
  - Young, John C., 1976-1981 (Box 71)
  - Youths, 1975 (Box 71)
- Notes (Boxes 72-73)
  - General, undated (Box 72)
  - Aristotle (Box 73)
  - Augustine, Saint, Bishop of Hippo (Box 73)
  - Bonhoeffer, Dietrich (Box 73)
  - Cicero (Box 73)
  - Einsatzgruppen (Box 73)
  - Kütemeyer, Wilhelm (Box 73)
  - Leibrecht, Walter (Box 73)
  - Lewis, C.S. (Box 73)
  - Marx, Karl (Box 73)
  - Portmann, Adolf (Box 73)
  - Rahner, Karl, 1966-1967 (Box 73)
  - Ramsey, Ian (Box 73)
  - Ramsey, Paul (Box 73)
  - Random thoughts (Box 73)
  - Schwabe, Gerhard (Box 73)
  - Thomas, Aquinas, Saint (Box 73)
  - Veblen, Thorstein (Box 73)